- Howard wolowitz.
- Hey.
(Voice:)Dave Roeger, here, at NASA. We need
to talk about your upcoming mission.
(Howard:)Yes, yes, I've been doing
my push-ups.
(Howard:)I'm still stuck at nine, but...
(Howard:)That's going all the way down
with no one holding me, heh.
(Roeger:)That's great, uh, but that's not why I called.
(Roeger:)We've run into a bit of a snafu.
(Roeger:)Your Soyuz capsule failed
the pressurization test...
(Roeger:)...so bottom line,
the mission's been scrubbed.
(Howard(Picks up receiver):)You're kidding.
So, what does that mean?
(Howard(Picks up receiver):)Uh-huh.
Uh-huh, heh.
Boy, I gotta tell you,
I'm really disappointed.
(Howard(Picks up receiver):)This was my dream
ever since I was a little kid.
Okay, uh... Thanks for the call.
Yeah, you too.
(Howard(Picks up receiver):)Yes! Thank you!
Oh, I'm not gonna die in space!
Phew, I'm gonna die the way God intended.
(Howard(Picks up receiver):)In my late 50s
with a heart full of pastrami.